Logan Moody

Full-Stack Developer

(419) 340-5630 lbmoody3@gmail.com



Profile:

Full stack developer with experience with Angular and React. I have a passion for excellence in ux/ui design with 5+ years of professional experience in a dynamic team environment focused on building web applications that are intuitive, improve user interaction and create company-changing efficiencies.

Skills & Technologies:

Angular React Node Javascript Typescript PHP Photoshop Illustrator XD

AWS Agile Git Docker MongoDB MySQL

Experience:

Continuum Health Solutions

Jan 2013 - Present

Full-Stack Developer

Feb 2020- Present

Currently working on converting legacy php applications to angular/php (yii framework) applications while gaining experience with docker and aws environments.

Front-End
Developer & UX/UI
Designer

Sept 2017-Feb 2020

Used Angular 4/5 6/7, Bootstrap, and Material to build in-house web-based applications with Restful API interfacing for everyday employee use. Led the process to re-think, re-design, and build new tools for staff to use daily, utilizing previous company knowledge and shadowing of current employees.

Project Manager June 2015 - July 2018 Working with company executives and development team to both improve system efficiencies and implement new tools. Organized and maintained tasks for new client implementations. Collaborated with client executives and managers for implementations and maintaining daily operations.

System Analyst

Jan 2015 - Dec 2016

Learned and re-thought data processing for Continuum while spending time understanding and gaining a knowledge of the technical aspects of the business through data processing and SQL reporting.

Education:

DU Fullstack Bootcamp, Mar 2020

Colorado Christian University, Lakewood, CO Bachelor of Arts, Biblical Studies. Graduated Spring 2012.